mirror.me 2011-12-03

# mirror.me | Privacy

### Mirror.me Privacy Notices

Last updated: November 15, 2010

This document outlines our policy with respect to the information we gather from third party websites and the information we collect once you visit our website. Given the nature of our website we are extremely sensitive to the privacy concerns of our website visitors and users of our service. We also know that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. We have designed our policy around the expectations that we ourselves would expect from a service such as ours.

By visiting the mirror.me website you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

If you have any questions or concerns please contact us. Email is best (privacy@mirror.me), but we can also be reached at our address: 60 Hazelwood Dr., Suite 107, Champaign, IL 61820.

##### Third Party Websites

To compile your Reflection we aggregate public data from various websites. These currently include: Twitter.com, Facebook.com, LinkedIn.com. Unless you grant us special permission we only access information that is publicly available. For example, if your Twitter account is private we can only gather a name, photo, and your Friends and Followers. Similarly with Facebook we are only able to access that information which you have designated as public. We do not exercise any control over these websites, their privacy policies, or privacy settings. If you would like to restrict what information is presented in your mirror.me Reflection you can change the privacy settings on these sites.

mirror.me may contain links to other websites. We encourage all users to read the privacy policies of each and every website visited when following links from the mirror.me website. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by mirror.me.

##### The Information We Collect

We may collect both personally identifiable information about you and non-personally-identifiable information about your experience when you access the mirror.me website.

The personally identifiable information we collect on our website or through our service consists of information you submit to us, including your name, email address, and other personal information that you willingly provide. Because participation in these activities is voluntary, you have a choice whether or not to disclose such information.

In addition to information that you provide to us through forms, we receive non-personally identifiable information whenever you interact with our websites, including your Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type and version, geographical region, referral URLs, and other data automatically supplied by common web browsers.

At this time you are not able to register an account on our site. To access personalized features on our site you must sign in with your Twitter or Facebook accounts.

##### How Is Your Information Used?

Information about our users is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We do not sell, rent, or lease your information to third parties.

The information we obtain from mirror.me users helps us enhance and refine our service and content. Non-personal information collected about you through your experience and queries is used to better understand the entire population that is utilizing our website and how we might improve our services to improve the collective experience. Except as noted below, we track and record IP addresses that access our website for internal reporting, diagnostic, and analysis purposes only.

If you choose to receive communication from mirror.me directly or via use of any submission forms associated with the website, we may send you an email response as well as notify you of other offers or services that may be of interest. When you send email or other communications to us, we may retain those communications to respond to you and improve our products and services.

Your IP address is used to determine, when possible, your approximate geographical location, which affects such things as your search results. Your browser type may be used to fine-tune the results for optimal display, for example on mobile devices or to work around limitations of a particular browser. Referrer URLs may be used to generate usage statistics and analyze usage patterns.

##### Other Disclosures of Your Information

We may employ other companies and individuals (agents) to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include analyzing data, processing payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

We may send offers to selected groups of mirror.me users on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give that business your personal information. If you do not want to receive such offers, we will give you the opportunity to unsubscribe to them.

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy additional services or business units. In such transactions, user information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Notice (unless, of course, the user consents otherwise). Also, in the event that mirror.me or substantially all of its assets are acquired, user information will of course be one of the transferred assets.

We may release personally identifying information when we believe release is necessary to comply with lawful court orders. Any collected information associated with your use of the website (personal and non-personal) will be disclosed to government authorities or third parties only pursuant to a lawful request, subpoena, or other process that legally compels disclosure of that information.

We may also preserve, use, or disclose your information if necessary to enforce our Terms of Use and related agreements; to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, including high-volume use of the website; to respond to support requests; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of mirror.me, our users, or others.

##### Cookies

When you visit our website, we, like most websites, send one or more cookies—small anonymous identifiers—to your computer that uniquely identify you to our servers. While we do use cookies for security and fraud investigation purposes, our primary purpose is to enhance your user experience by understanding and remembering your preferences, and by general tracking of our user trends.

##### A few more words on Cookies

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers (a small text file) that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as personalization.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or to notify you when a cookie is sent. Please be aware that mirror.me may not have full functionality if your browser refuses cookies.

##### Accessing mirror.me from Third-Party Sources

mirror.me may additionally be accessed through web widgets or gadgets that are embedded on third-party sites. If you choose to access mirror.me via such tools, then depending on the third-party widget technology, your personal information and queries may be passed on to the third party's servers prior to being processed on the mirror.me website.

##### Security

We take appropriate measures to ensure the security of our website and systems. This includes precautions to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, or destruction of data.

Despite our efforts to protect your personal information, there is always some risk that an unauthorized third party may find a way around our security systems or that transmissions of your information over the internet may be intercepted. Your use of the website constitutes an acceptance of such risk.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

##### Your Choices

As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to take advantage of the mirror.me site.

You can add or update certain information, such as connecting your other social account by going to the “Settings feature of the Web site. When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records.

The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, your use of the mirror.me website will be hampered if you do not use cookies.

##### Children

Use of the mirror.me site is limited to persons and entities that lawfully can enter into and form contracts under applicable law.  It is not intended for use by minors.

##### Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update or modify this Privacy Policy from time to time in the future. Any such updates or modifications shall be effective immediately upon their posting. Please refer back to this page often for the latest information.

##### Additional Resources

The Federal Trade commission provides additional information on Privacy and Security on its website: <http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/menus/consumer/tech/privacy.shtm>.
